It's super effective!
Requiescat in pace.
You have died of dysentery.
The cake is a lie.
War. War never changes.
A man chooses, a slave obeys.
I used to be an adventurer like you.
It's dangerous to go alone.
Do a barrel roll!
Praise the sun!
You're gonna need a bigger boat.
Elementary, my dear Watson.
May the Force be with you.
I'll be back.
Here's looking at you, kid.
To infinity and beyond!
After all this time? Always.
Not all those who wander are lost.
The night is darkest just before the dawn.
Stay hungry, stay foolish.
Less is more.
Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication.
The best way out is always through.
Turn your wounds into wisdom.
What we think, we become.
Whatever you are, be a good one.
Do one thing every day that scares you.
The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step.
Starry, starry night.
Paint the sky, make it yours.
